Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Records WAG.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Other Unions/Guilds/Federations
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Canceling of Affiliation Agreement and SAG Basic Contract with Agents, 1939 (Box 333, Folder 18)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Constitution and By-Laws (also By-Laws from 1945), 1981, 1983 (Box 333, Folder 19)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 333, Folder 20)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence, 1947 (Box 333, Folder 21)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence, 1948 (Box 333, Folder 22)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence (and related materials including SAG Agency Regulations Effective Nov. 1, 1949) (Box 333, Folder 23)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence (and related materials including SAG Contract Demands for Television pamphlet), 1950 (Box 333, Folder 24)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence, 1951 (Box 333, Folder 25)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence (and related materials), 1952 (Box 333, Folder 26)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence (and related materials), 1953 (Box 334, Folder 1)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence, 1954 (Box 334, Folder 2)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence (and related materials including New York Extras Agreement), 1955-1956 (Box 334, Folder 3)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence (and related materials), 1957-1958 (Box 334, Folder 4)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence (and related materials including Commercials Contract and Memorandum of Agreement for Theatrical Motion Pictures)), 1960 (Box 334, Folder 5)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence (and related materials including 1966 Dubbing Agreement), 1961-1966 (Box 334, Folder 6)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence (and related materials), 1967-1970 (Box 334, Folder 7)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Correspondence (and related materials including Basic and Television Agreements for 1977), 1973-1974, 1977, 1979 (Box 334, Folder 8)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): General (including Television and Dubbing Agreements), 1980-1981 (Box 334, Folder 9)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): General (including Industrial/Educational and Commercial Contracts), 1982 (Box 334, Folder 10)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): General, 1983-1985 (Box 334, Folder 11)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Resolution Condemning Senate Interstate Commerce Sub-Committee Investigation of Motion Picture Industry, 1941 (Box 334, Folder 12)
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG): Rules and Procedures of the New York Branch, 1955, 1965 (Box 334, Folder 13)
  - Screen Directors Guild: General, 1951 (Box 334, Folder 14)
  - Screen Extras Guild (SEG): correspondence, agreements and related materials (not all years included), 1945-1973 (Box 334, Folder 15)
  - Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers (SSD&C): Correspondence and related materials, 1960-1970 (Box 334, Folder 16)
  - SSD&C: Correspondence and related materials, 1973-1974 (Box 334, Folder 17)
  - Theatrical Wardrobe Attendants Union, Local 764, 1947 (Box 334, Folder 18)
  - Unions: General, 1947, 1958 (Box 334, Folder 19)
  - United Scenic Artists, Local 829, 1947-1948 (Box 334, Folder 20)
  - United Scenic Artists, Local 350, 1971-1973 (Box 334, Folder 21)
- Series VIII: Oversized/Scrapbooks
  On occasion members of Equity staff put together scrapbooks. Included here are three including one for the 1960 strike, one for Chorus Equity and one from executive Paul Dullzell.
  - Broadway Blackout scrapbook and clippings, 1960 (Box 334A)
  - Scrapbooks, 1948-1949 (Box 334B)
- Series IX: Archived Website, Sep 23, 2007-ongoing
  Actors' Equity Association ("AEA" or "Equity"), founded in 1913, is the labor union that represents more than 48,000 actors and stage managers in the United States. Equity seeks to advance, promote and foster the art of live theatre as an essential component of our society. Equity negotiates wages and working conditions and provides a wide range of benefits, including health and pension plans, for its members. Actors' Equity is a member of the AFL-CIO, and is affiliated with FIA, an international organization of performing arts unions. The website contains their newsletter, Equity News, news listings, member benefits, agreements, election information, and meeting listings.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
- Series X: Photographs, Video, and Ephemera, 1913-1991; 3 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 2 manuscript boxes
  Consists of photographs of Actors' Equity Association members and events, clippings, invitations, publications, playbills, musical scores, piano practice books, scripts, and pins.
  The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  - Ephemera, 1913-1961 (Box 362)
  - Ephemera, 1932-1966 (Box 360)
  - Photographs and Ephemera, 1921-1968 (Box 366)
  - Photographs and Ephemera, 1929-1991 (Box 361)
  - Video: "Faces", undated (Box Shared Tamiment 015)